She was looking to model. She found evil instead.
A Model Kidnapping is a thriller, tv movie, crime film directed by Damián Romay.
Grace, an aspiring model, is thrilled to have fashion
photographer Hunter Kelly help launch her career.
But when Grace is held against her will, Hunter’s true intention to use
her as his next “star” on a sexy website is revealed.
With courage and resourcefulness, Grace must now find a way to escape
before she becomes Hunter’s next model murder victim.
Inspired by true events.
Grace, played by Lucy Loken.
Hunter Kelly, played by Wes McGee.
Detective Hogan, played by Gary Bristow.
Nicole, played by Katherine Diaz.
Kelsey, played by Jessica Galinas.
Mark Harding, played by Seth Goodfellow.
The abduction of Chloe Ayling occurred in July 2017 while Ayling, a British page
3 model, had travelled to Milan, Italy, for a fake photo-shoot.
There, she was abducted by two people claiming to be members of a
criminal organisation called The Black Death Group.
In June 2018, Łukasz Herba, a Polish national from the United Kingdom, was convicted in a
Milan court of the kidnapping and sentenced to 16 years and 9 months in prison.
The film explores themes of kidnapping, killing, murder, model, held hostage.
The tone is intense.